eternalwarcry.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy | Eternal Warcry

  1. Home
  2.  About 
  3. Privacy Policy

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit eternalwarcry.com?

Google analytics is used throughout eternalwarcry.com 

### When and what information do we collect?

For any personal information, we collect and store that when you register on eternalwarcry.com. Your name, email, and password will never be shared with a third party vendor. Your passwords are hashed and protected. Even the programmer who created the site cannot reverse your password. 

### How do we use your information?

Your account is used to better enhance your experience on eternalwarcry.com as certain features will not work unless you are logged in. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

They're also used to understand and save user's preferences for future visits. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. 

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly. 

### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. 

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
